

# HARD SKILLS

DS Python & SQL (still learning) Main Microsoft office Advance Mathemetic&Statistic Mainstream Economics Some Business & Management

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Communication with people Collaboration with team Creativity Critical thinking & Problem Solving Planner & Learner Focus & Futuristic

# INTEREST

Math & Statistic
Coding
The Power Of Data
Technology & Business
Experiment
Global Trend
Environment

# ATITUDE

Focus on flexibility rather than perfection.
Focus on results rather than methods

### CONTACT

champmaster1999@outlook.com 082-487-2384

728/9 Village No.11 Sukhumvit Road, Klongdan Sub-district, Bangbo District, Samutprakan, 10550

# NOPPADON WATCHALACHAITRAKUL

# Intern-Data scientist

# **PROFILE**

Economics students that have interested in math, statistics and business until I studied econometrics subject ,which is a subject that finds the correlation of data and else. I also follow the world trends until I met with a career as a Data Scientist ,which is close to the subjects that I'm interested but I must need to study more programs ex. DS Python , SQL , Tableau and business knowlegde. It's amazing for me! Therefore I have started to study "Data Scientist with Python (CAREER TRACK)" for 10 month on DataCamp and readed article/book about Bigdata project. Now I'm ready to learn with you. Learn to work with your team and your projects. Test me and give me the first opportunity to do an internship with you to give me experience. I believe that you will get a powerful person.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **ECONOMETRICS PROJECT (FIND RELATION BETWEEN FACTORS)**

Applie Econometrics | Sep. - Oct. 2020 Find Factors that affects "interest to study a master's degre" (Binary Regression Model) by using program of economics (gretl.)

#### SHAREHOLDER MEETING REGISTRAR (PART-TIME)

Inventech Systems co., Itd. | August 2020

# MULTI-LEVEL MARKETING BUSINESSMAN (FREELANCE)

Amway (Thailand) Ltd. | February 2019 - present

#### WAITER WITH TEAM (PART-TIME)

i do Catering | August 2019 - present

# **EDUCATION**

# BACHELOR OF ECONOMICS, MAJOR IN ECOMONICS (FOCUS MATH & STATISTIC & BUSINESS) PRESENT GPA 3.84

Srinakharinwirot University | 2018 - present

# DATA SCIENTIST WITH PYTHON (CAREER TRACK)

DataCamp | July 2020 - present

Now I can and understand: Import Data, Clean Data, Manipulate Data (Pandas), Visualze Data (Matplotlib, Seaborn), Write Function, Test Hyhothesis, Basic Supervised Learning, Basic Unsupervised Learning, Decision Tree Next, I'm learning about intermediate Machine Learning, Cluster Analysis and learning to create Data Project.

# **CERTIFICATE & ACTIVITY**

### **CERTIFICATE OF DATA SCIENTIST WITH PYTHON**

DataCamp | 2020-present (still learning)



# CERTIFICATE OF ACADEMIC EXCELLENCE (1-YEAR AND 2-YEAR)

Faculty of Economics Srinakharinwirot University | 2018-2019

#### **ACTIVITIES IN COLLEGE LIFE**

ex. University Show, Freshmen Orientation, Volunteer Camp and else.



# SRINAKHARINWIROT UNIVERSITY

114 SUKHUMVIT 23, BANGKOK 10110, THAILAND

# Official Transcript of Academic Record

Student ID No.: 61149010131

Birthdate: July 26, 1999

Date of Addmission: August 14, 2018

Date of Graduation:

Name: MR.NOPPADON WATCHALACHAITRAKUL

Faculty: Faculty of Economics

Degree: B.Econ.

Field of Study: Economics

Page 1 of 1

Qualification for Admission: Matayom Suksa VI

Remarks:

ECC341

ECC371

S0331

SWU261

MONEY AND BANKING

ACTIVE CITIZENS

MANAGERIAL ECONOMICS

THAI TRADITIONS AND RELIGIONS

- - - - - - - - END OF COLUMN-

	Course	Credi	t Grade	7	Course	Credit Grade
	FIRST SEMESTER 2018				SEM GPA 3.80 PASS CR 22.00	
ECC100	PRINCIPLES OF ECONOMICS	3	A		ACCUM GPA 3.80 PASS CR 74.00	
ECC111	MATHEMATICAL ECONOMICS I	3	A			
SWU121	ENGLISH FOR EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATION	3	B+	1 1	FIRST SEMESTER 2020	
	I	1	01			
SWU132	PERSONAL FITNESS	1	B+	ECC302	INTERMEDIATE MACROECONOMICS	4 A
SWU141	LIFE IN A DIGITAL WORLD	3	B+	ECC312	APPLIED ECONOMETRICS	3 A
SWU151	GENERAL EDUCATION FOR HUMAN	3	A	ECC351	INTERNATIONAL ECONOMICS	3 A
	DEVELOPMENT		^	ECC443	CORPORATE FINANCE	3 A
	SEM GPA 3.78 PASS CR 16.00			ECC474	CREATIVE ECONOMY	3 A
	ACCUM GPA 3.78 PASS CR 16.00			SWU247	FOOD FOR LIFE	2 A
	20.00				SEM GPA 4.00 PASS CR 18.00	
	( )				ACCUM GPA 3.84 PASS CR 92.00	
	SECOND SEMESTER 2018					
ECC101	INTRODUCTION TO MICROECONOMICS	3	A		SECOND SEMESTER 2020	
ECC112	STATISTICS FOR ECONOMISTS	3	A .	ECC413	TIME SERIES ECONOMETRICS	3
SWU111	THAI FOR COMMUNICATION	3	В	ECC442	PRINCIPLES OF INVESTMENTS	3
SWU122	ENGLISH FOR EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATION	3	B+	ECC453	INTERNATIONAL MONETARY ECONOMICS	3
	II			ECC455	ECONOMICS OF SELECTED COUNTRIES	3
SWU131	SOCIAL DANCE	1	Α	ECC462	INDUSTRIAL ORGANIZATION	
SWU161	HUMAN IN LEARNING SOCIETY	2	B+	ECC464	BEHAVIORAL ECONOMICS	3
	SEM GPA 3.63 PASS CR 15.00			SWU354	CREATIVITY AND INNOVATION	3
	ACCUM GPA 3.71 PASS CR 31.00			3110334		3
	FIRST SEMESTER 2019					
CUDIOC					TRANSCRIPT INCOMPLETE	
CMD106	CREATIVE THINKING FOR COMMUNICATION	3	Α			
F00000	DESIGN					math & statist
ECC202	INTRODUCTION TO MACROECONOMICS	3	Α		The state of the s	
ECC211	MATHEMATICAL ECONOMICS II	3	Α		2 1 M	Business
ECC321	DEVELOPMENT ECONOMICS	3	A	and the same of		2 2 2 1
ECC331	HUMAN RESOURCE ECONOMICS	3	A	05	jur econometric	שן בחו עבונ חיפ
ECC361	INDUSTRIAL ECONOMICS	3	Α	100	ves data science	Pens ter a.
SWU244	SCIENCE FOR BETTER LIFE AND	3	B+	9 9 9 9	E framodel, m	
	ENVIRONMENT				w, laboutels &	1410 0 096
	SEM GPA 3.93 PASS CR 21.00			A CONTRACTOR OF THE PARTY OF TH	ราอารถ วัดการสิงมู	
	ACCUM GPA 3.80 PASS CR 52.00				•	
					na: visualizati	on
	SECOND SEMESTER 2019				to me sir math	1 - dd - di - 1
ECC201		4	^		Man (1) aby may b	+ 5 707/5116 +
ECC201	INTERMEDIATE MICROECONOMICS THAI ECONOMY	4	A			
ECC212		3	A			
LUCZIZ	INTRODUCTION TO ECONOMETRICS	3	A			

בורוש מלים ביאה מיפלים בנו בו בו בים בים בים בים בים בים

stict business data

Banchar Nimprasert (Mr) Registrar Data Issued : 30 December 2020

A

B

A

B+

3

3